
Atomic energy might be as good as our present-day explosives,
but it is unlikely to produce anything very much more dangerous.
[AlignRight]-- Winston Churchill, British Prime Minister, 1939.

There is at least one thing worse than fighting with allies -
And that is to fight without them.
[AlignRight]-- Winston Churchill

The power of an air force is terrific when there is nothing to oppose it.
[AlignRight]-- Winston Churchill

The only thing that ever frightened me during the war was the U-Boat peril.
[AlignRight]-- Winston Churchill

Strength lies not in defense, but in attack.
[AlignRight]-- Adolf Hitler, Mein Kampf

People never lie so much as after a hunt, during a war or before an election.
[AlignRight]-- Otto Von Bismarck

Though we have heard of stupid haste in war,
cleverness has never been seen associated with long delays.
[AlignRight]-- Sun Tzu, the Art of War

So in war, the way is to avoid what is strong
and to strike at what is weak.
[AlignRight]-- Sun Tzu, the Art of War

A military operation involves deception. Even though you are competent,
appear to be incompetent. Though effective, appear to be ineffective.
[AlignRight]-- Sun Tzu, the Art of War

Everything which the enemy least expects will succeed the best.
[AlignRight]-- Frederick the Great

Airplanes are interesting toys but of no military value.
[AlignRight]-- Marshal Ferdinand Foch, circa 1911

If you entrench yourself behind strong fortifications,
you compel the enemy seek a solution elsewhere.
[AlignRight]-- Karl von Clausewitz

Political power grows out of the barrel of a gun.
[AlignRight]-- Mao Zedong

May God have mercy upon my enemies, because I won't.
[AlignRight]-- General George Patton

Fixed fortifications are monuments to the stupidity of man.
[AlignRight]-- General George Patton

The enemy is but weeds to be moved.
[AlignRight]-- Aztec Proverb

Put your trust in God, but keep your powder dry.
[AlignRight]-- Oliver Cromwell

The God of War hates those who hesitate.
[AlignRight]-- Euripides

He who stays on the defensive does not make war, he endures it.
[AlignRight]-- Field Marshal Colmar Baron von der Goltz

One cannot simultaneously prevent and prepare for war.
[AlignRight]-- Albert Einstein
To be prepared for war is one of the most effectual means
of preserving peace.
[AlignRight]-- George Washington

Quantity has a quality all its own.
[AlignRight]-- Joseph Stalin

British declare german uboat attacks "not very sporting".
[AlignRight]-- The Onion

When I lost my rifle, the Army charged me 85 dollars.
That is why in the Navy the Captain goes down with the ship.
[AlignRight]-- Dick Gregory

God is not on the side of the big battalions,
but on the side of those who shoot best.
[AlignRight]-- Voltaire

Politics is war without bloodshed,
while war is politics with bloodshed.
[AlignRight]-- Mao Zedong

In the eyes of empire builders men are not men but instruments.
[AlignRight]-- Napoleon

Gentlemen, we are being killed on the beaches.
Let us go inland and be killed.
[AlignRight]-- General Cota, Omaha Beach, June 6, 1944.

When the British shoot, the Germans duck,
when the Germans shoot, the British duck,
when the Americans shoot, everybody ducks.
[AlignRight]-- Old World War II saying

Any time you think you're smarter than your adversary,
you're probably about a half-mile from the Little Big Horn.
[AlignRight]-- Colonel Art Corbett, USMC

They couldn't hit an elephant at this distance.
[AlignRight]-- John Sedgwick, seconds before being shot

veni, vidi, vici
( I came, I saw, I conquered. )
[AlignRight]-- Julius Caesar

Twenty-five [combat missions] doesn't sound like much until you start flying them.
[AlignRight]-- Cpt Robert Morgan of the Memphis Belle,
[AlignRight]first US heavy bomber to complete 25 combat missions
